thegtaplace.com 2018-12-15

# The GTA Place - Privacy Policy

### Introduction

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors and service users. This policy applies where we are acting as a data controller with respect to the personal data of our website visitors and service users; in other words, where we determine the purposes and means of the processing of that personal data.

In this policy, "we", "us" and "our" are terms used to refer to this website ("The GTA Place", also known as "TGTAP") and "app" is a term used to refer to our mobile application ("Cheats for GTA"), collectively these are referred to as our "Services".

## Information we collect and why

In order to provide you with our Services, we collect certain information from you when you use our Services. We will hold the above information for as long as is necessary in order to provide you with our services, deal with any specific issues that you may raise or otherwise as is required by law or any relevant regulatory body.

### Information we collect about you

  * **Personal Information**  — By using our Services, we may collect the following categories of personal information ("personal information") you provide to us: username; email address; and optionally: real name; date of birth; gender; contact information and other information you provide through our Services; and other information you may provide about yourself or others through our Services or to which you provide us with access via third-party platform.
  * **Device Information**  —When you use our Services or open communications (such as emails), some information is automatically collected from devices (e.g., mobile, computer, laptop, tablet) used to visit or use our Services including, but not limited to, operating system, access times, unique device identifiers, service provider, IP address, screen resolution, browser type, language, referring site and other data about your device that we use to provide the services or as otherwise described in this Policy ("device information"). We also collect information about your usage and activity on our Services using certain technologies, such as cookies, web beacons and other technologies.
  * **Location Information**  — If you use our Services, we may receive and store your generic location (such as city or neighbourhood) for the purposes of analytics. We will collect location information based on, for example, your IP address, to provide anonymous analytical information on the geographical distribution (city level) of our visitors and users around the world.
  * **Usage Information**  — We collect certain anonymous analytical information when you use our Services, including information about your interaction with the Services, including the actions you take on the Services.
  * **Cookies**  — we may also collect certain information through the use of “cookies”. Cookies are small files that your browser places on your computer. We may use session cookies, persistent cookies, and other tracking technologies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies from the websites you visit.

### How we use your information

We may process your account data ("account data"). The account data may include your email address. The source of the account data is either yourself when registering for an account on our website, or via a third party connection such as Facebook or Twitter. We use information held about you (and information about others) in the following ways:

  * to provide you with our services;
  * to ensure the content on our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer or mobile device;
  * to notify you about changes to our service; and
  * maintaining back-ups of our databases.

The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business.

We may process your information included in your personal profile on our website ("profile data"). The profile data may include your name, email address, profile pictures, date of birth, interests and hobbies that you optionally provide. The profile data may be processed for the purposes of enabling and monitoring your use of our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business.

We may process information that you post for publication on our website or through our services ("publication data"). The publication data may be processed for the purposes of enabling such publication and administering our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business.

### How we share your information

For our effective operation and to deliver our Services to you we may share information with Third Parties.

We may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person. We may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.

### What information we share, who we share it with and why

  * We may process data about your use of our website and services (" **usage data** "). The usage data may include your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of the usage data is our analytics tracking system. This usage data may be processed for the purposes of analysing the use of the website and services. The legal basis for this processing is consent or our legitimate interests, namely monitoring and improving our website and services.

  * Device and usage information of our app will be shared with Google Analytics (Google), Apple Analytics (Apple) and Crashlytics (Fabric, a Google company) for analytics and crash reporting.

  * We may process your personal data that is provided in the course of the use of our services (" **service data** "). The service data may include the timing, frequency and pattern of service use. The source of the service data is you. The service data may be processed for the purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring the security of our website and services, maintaining back-ups of our databases and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business.

  * We may process information that you post for publication on our website or through our services (" **publication data** "). The publication data may be processed for the purposes of enabling such publication and administering our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business.

  * We may process information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters (" **notification data** "). The notification data may be processed for the purposes of sending you the relevant notifications and/or newsletters. The legal basis for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.

  * We may process information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us (" **correspondence data** "). The correspondence data may include the communication content and metadata associated with the communication. Our website will generate the metadata associated with communications made using the website contact forms. The correspondence data may be processed for the purposes of communicating with you and record-keeping. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business and communications with users.

  * In addition to the specific purposes for which we may process your personal data set out in this section, we may also process any of your personal data where such processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

  * Please do not supply any other person's personal data to us, unless we prompt you to do so.

### Cookies that we use and why

We uses cookies to distinguish you from other users on our website. Some of these cookies are essential for certain features of this website to function properly, including the ability to register and login to your account, save your preferences, and enable you to post on our forums and communicate with other members. Insofar as those cookies are not strictly necessary for the provision of our website and services, we will ask you to consent to our use of cookies when you first visit our website.

Should you choose to decline the use of cookies, or later remove cookies that have been set, your use of our website will be limited in that you will not be able to access functionality that requires a logged in account.

We use cookies for the following purposes:

(a) authentication - we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website;

(b) status - we use cookies to help us to determine if you are logged into our website;

(c) security - we use cookies as an element of the security measures used to protect user accounts, including preventing fraudulent use of login credentials, and to protect our website and services generally;

(d) advertising - we use cookies to help us to display advertisements that will be relevant to you (cookies used for this purpose are: Google AdSense, Google AdExchange, Avocet, PulsePoint, Teads, Skimlinks, Monetizer 101);

(e) analysis - we use cookies to help us to analyse the use and performance of our website and services (cookies used for this purpose are: Google Analytics, ComScore, Google Tag Manager, Crazy Egg, Facebook Audience, Google Analytics Audience);

(f) cookie consent - we use cookies to store your preferences in relation to the use of cookies more generally. 

## Your Data and Rights

### Information Disclosure

  * We may disclose your personal data to any member of our group of companies (this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes, and on the legal bases, set out in this policy.

  * We may disclose your personal data to our insurers and/or professional advisers insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, obtaining professional advice, or the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.

  * In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this Section, we may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person. We may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.

### International transfers of your personal data

The hosting facilities for our website are situated in the UK. The European Commission has made an "adequacy decision" with respect to the data protection laws of each of these countries. Transfers to each of these countries will be protected by appropriate safeguards, namely EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. 

Mailing databases are situated in the UK. The European Commission has made an "adequacy decision" with respect to the data protection laws of each of these countries. Transfers to each of these countries will be protected by appropriate safeguards, namely EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield.

You acknowledge that personal data that you submit for publication through our website or services may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use (or misuse) of such personal data by others.

### Retaining and deleting personal data

Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes. Cookie data will be retained for no longer than 100 days.

We may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

If you would like us to delete your personal data, you can do so by contacting us at the email address given at the end of this Policy, alternatively you can log in to our forums and either use the Contact Us link in the footer or send a private message to one of the listed Administrators.

### Your Rights

We have summarised the rights that you have under data protection law. Some of the rights are complex, and not all of the details have been included in our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of these rights.

Your principal rights under data protection law are:

  * the right to access;
  * the right to rectification;
  * the right to erasure;
  * the right to restrict processing;
  * the right to object to processing;
  * the right to data portability;
  * the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and
  * the right to withdraw consent.

**Access** \- You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information. That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable administration fee.

**Rectification** \- You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.

**Erasure** \- In some circumstances you have the right to the erasure of your personal data without undue delay. Those circumstances include: the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed; you withdraw consent to consent-based processing; you object to the processing under certain rules of applicable data protection law; the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and the personal data have been unlawfully processed. However, there are exclusions of the right to erasure. The general exclusions include where processing is necessary: for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; for compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

**Restriction** \- In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest.

**Objection** \- You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

**Data portability** \- You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal data for this purpose.

**Complaining** \- If you consider that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.

**Consent withdrawal** \- To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.

You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by contacting us using the details provided at the end of the Policy.

## Managing Cookies

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:

(a) https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en (Chrome);  
(b) https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences (Firefox);  
(c) http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/ (Opera);  
(d) https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies (Internet Explorer);  
(e) https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411 (Safari); and  
(f) https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy (Edge).

## Third Party Services

Our service providers use cookies and those cookies may be stored on your computer when you visit our website. In addition to the Services we provide directly, we also use third party service providers (collectively referred to as “Third Party Services”) who operate their own Privacy Policies. The Third Party Services we use we deem important to our effective operation.

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of our website and app. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google's privacy policy is available at: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

### Google AdSense and Google AdMob

We publish Google AdMob advertisements in our app. We publish Google AdSense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the AdSense partner network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative's multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you may wish to consider using the Google browser plug-ins available at: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996>.

### Interest-based ads

We use Avocet, OpenX, PulsePoint, Sovrn and Google Audiences to carry out retargeting and Header Bidding. These service uses cookies for retargeting ads and targeting ads based on your interests. You can view the privacy policy of these service providers at <http://avocet.io/privacy-policy>, <https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/>, <https://www.pulsepoint.com/privacy-policy.html>, <https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/> and <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>.

### Crashlytics

Our app utilises Crashlytics, a service provided by Fabric, a Google company. Crashlytics is an analytics tool that helps mobile application developers analyse, diagnose and fix crashes experiences by users of their applications. Crashlytics collects information anonymously. It reports application crash details including device information without identifying individual users. Crashlytics' privacy policy can be found at <https://fabric.io/terms>.

### MoPub

We use MoPub to publish advertisements in our app. MoPub's privacy policy can be found at <https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/>.

### Microsoft Advertising

Cheats for GTA on the Windows platform is supported by ads from Microsoft Advertising. Learn more about Microsoft's privacy practices and your choices at <https://choice.microsoft.com/AdvertisementChoice/>.

### Links

The GTA Place contains links to third party web sites and resource. The GTA Place is not responsible for the content nor the privacy practises of other web sites and resources, and encourages you to read their privacy policy or statement as it may differ to this one.

### Contacting The GTA Place

If you have any questions about this policy please email data@thegtaplace.com.

### Changes to This Policy

We reserve the right to update or change this privacy policy at any time. Any such change, modification, or addition to the privacy policy on The GTA Place will become effective immediately upon posting on the site.

_Last modified: 19th May, 2018._
